Guide to Texas A&M University Catalogs, etc. Cubb.00220
Cubberley Education Library
Texas A&M University (formerly: Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas)
1901-1980
Cubberley Education Library
Cubb.00220
108 item(s)
Located in College Station, Texas. Founded as a land-grant college, opening in 1876 called Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas. In 1963 name changed to Texas A&M University.
Texas; Land-grant colleges; Technical colleges; Agricultural colleges
- Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas, 1901-1963; 78 item(s) Catalogs for 1901/02, 1903/04-1904/05, 1906/07-1909/10, 1911/12-1912/13, 1914/15-1926/27, 1928/29-1943/44, 1947/48-1948/49, 1950/51, 1952/53-1956/57, 1958/59-1959/60 Announcements for 1915/16-1916/17, 1918/19
  - Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas: Summer Session, 1910-1935; 13 item(s) Bulletins for 1910-1911, 1917-1918, 1920-1925, 1927, 1935
  - Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas: Graduate School, 1925-1963; 6 item(s) Bulletins for 1925/26, 1948/49, 1951/52, 1953/55, 1959/60, 1962/63
  - Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas: Annual Report, 1919-1920; 1 item(s) Reports for 1919/20
  - North Texas Agricultural College (Branch of Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas): Annual Report, 1922-1926; 3 item(s) Reports for 1922/23, 1924/25-1925/26
  - Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas: Bulletin of Information, 1925-30; 2 item(s) Bulletin for 1925/26, 1929/30
  - Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas: General Information, 1945/46; 1 item(s) Catalog for 1945/46
  - Supplement to First Five Administrators of Texas A&M College: James Reid Cole by David Brooks Cofer, College Archivist, 1955; 1 item(s)
  - Proceedings of the Inauguration of James Earl Rudder as President of the Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas, March 23, 1960; 1 item(s)
  - Agricultural and Mechanical College of Texas: The Semi-Centennial Celebration and The Inauguration of Thomas Otto Walton, LL.D. as President of the College, Oct. 15-17, 1926; 1 item(s) Oct. 15-17, 1926.
- Texas A&M University, 1962-1980; 29 item(s) Catalogs for 1962/63-1965/66, 1967/68, 1969/70 Undergraduate Catalog for 1975/76
  - Texas A&M University: Graduate Catalog, 1963-1977; 7 item(s) Catalogs for 1963/64-1966/67, 1970/71, 1975/76-1976/77
  - Texas A&M University System: Annual Report, 1962-1966; 4 item(s) Reports for 1962/63-1965/66
  - Texas A&M University: Faculty Publications, 1966-1969; 2 item(s) Lists for 1966/67 & 1968/69
  - Texas A&M University System: Financial Report, 1963-1967; 5 item(s) Reports for fiscal years ending 1963-1967
  - Water for Texas: Proceedings of Annual Conference, 1963-1966; 2 item(s) Proceedings from 1963 & 1966
  - Texas A&M University: Teaching, Research, Public Service, [1966]; 1 item(s) Pamphlet rec'd April 1966
  - Texas A&M University Library Annual Report, 1979-1980; 1 item(s) Report for 1979/80
  - Texas A&M University: Sea Grant College, 1971-1975; 4 item(s) Annual Report for 1974/75
    - Texas A&M University, Sea Grant College: The University & the Sea, 1973-1975; 3 item(s) Vol. 6, no. 2 &3, 1973; Vol. 8, no. 2, 1975